mol.com 2016-11-29

# MOL - Money Online | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Last modified: August 2014

#### Our Commitment

At MOL AccessPortal Sdn. Bhd. ("MOL"), we are extremely proud of our commitment to protect your privacy. We value your trust in us and assure you that we will use the information we collect only to provide a more personalized shopping experience. We will work hard to earn your confidence so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to friends and family. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offerings. 

#### Privacy guarantee

MOL promises never to rent, sell, share, barter or in any other way use personally identifiable information collected during your use of our MOLPoints without your prior permission (save as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy).

From time to time we may reveal general statistical information about our MOLPoints usage and visitors, such as number of visitors, number and type of goods and services purchased using MOLPoints, etc., but we will never reference you by name or specific personal information.

Your trust and confidence are our highest priority. 

#### Information we collect from you

When you use our services, we collect and store your personal information from you. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide an efficient, smooth and customized experience while using our services. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience easier and quicker.

In order to use our MOLPoints services, you will need to register at www.mol.com using our online registration form, where you will be required to provide us with certain information, namely your email address, account password, username and security question. You will not be able to use our MOLPoints services if you do not provide the required information and agree to the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy when prompted to do so. You will also be given the option to provide other personal information such as your identification number (which is required for refund requests and account related enquiries), gender, birthday, phone number and mailing address.

We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behavior on our site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address.

If you choose to purchase using MOLPoints, we collect information about your buying behavior. We also collect other users' comments about you in our feedback area. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

#### Our use of information collected from you

Registration Data and certain other information about you are subject to this Privacy Policy which is incorporated by reference into and made a part of our Terms of Service. By giving the Registration Data and certain other information about yourself to MOL, you agree and acknowledge that MOL may release such information to third parties as specified in this Privacy Policy, and that you give consent to such disclosure. 

Information we collect is used to build features that will make using our service an easier and more personal experience. This includes faster purchase requests, better customer support, improved product offerings and timely notice of new MOLPoints services and special offers. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs. 

We may also use your information to deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as new services and promotions. 

We may use your email address, your mailing address, and phone number to contact you regarding administrative notices, new product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of MOLPoints. 

#### Our Disclosure of your information

We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the site, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce the Terms of Service including this Privacy Policy. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular on rare occasions we may evaluate your information to look for users using multiple username or aliases.

Unfortunately, due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your username, name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email, and company as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will remain private.

#### How do we protect your information? 

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. 

#### What about children's privacy? 

Children are not eligible to use our services and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only with your parents or guardians permission/supervision.

#### Access or change your personally identifiable information

To protect your privacy and security, we will verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your personally identifiable information. If you wish to access, correct or limit the personally identifiable information you have submitted to us, you may update your profile online by logging into your account. If you have registered your profile at our www.mol.com site, your username and password are required in order to access your profile information.

#### General practices regarding use and storage of personal data 

You acknowledge that MOL may in its sole discretion establish general practices and limits concerning use of the MOLPoints services, including without limitation the manner in which the MOLPoints services may be used. You acknowledge that MOL reserves the right to close the accounts that are inactive for a period of seven (7) years and submit the unutilized MOLPoints balance in your account together with your personal information as required to the Registrar of Unclaimed Moneys. You further acknowledge that MOL reserves the right to modify these general practices and limits at any time, in its sole discretion, with or without notice, and you agree that your continued use of the MOLPoints services after such modification will constitute your acceptance of an agreement to be bound by the modified general practices and limits.

#### Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, we will employ reasonable and the latest Internet security methods and technologies.

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be communicated through our website at least 21 days prior written notice in advance of implementation. Information collected before changes are made will be secured according to the previous Privacy Policy. 

#### Your Consent

By using our MOLPoints, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by MOL. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

#### Talk to us

We welcome your questions and comments regarding our Privacy Policy. Please email our customer care support team at [helpdesk@mol.com](mailto:helpdesk@mol.com) or  click here for a list of contact details for the local customer care support team in your area.
